<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Desk Diver]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'll keep it brief.]]></description><link>https://twitter.com/andrewartajos</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:31:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Domino your debts]]></title><description><![CDATA[Domino Your Debts Today you’re going to regain control of your life. The bottom line is this: if you have a credit card debt, or a personal…]]></description><link>https://twitter.com/andrewartajos/domino-your-debts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://twitter.com/andrewartajos/domino-your-debts/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 23:45:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://barefootinvestor.com/barefoot-steps/step-3-domino-debts/&quot;&gt;Domino Your Debts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today you’re going to regain control of your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bottom line is this: if you have a credit card debt, or a personal loan, or a car loan, you’re not in control of your financial future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is step 3 of Scott Pape’s 9 steps to financial freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I started reading the book: The Barefoot Investor, we did not have any high interest debt. I always paid off my credit card in full every month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our goal was clear — save up for our home deposit.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But we took on bad debt last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We bought a seven seater Nissan Pathfinder through a car loan. We &lt;em&gt;needed&lt;/em&gt; a car to fit a family of five plus guests. We ended up getting $34K debt at 9.75% interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had some money stashed away for the home deposit. We kept paying minimum payments on the car loan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I did the math, the decision was obvious. We’re better off to use our saved up money which was $20K towards the car loan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am happy to report we’ll regain control of our lives by September 2019.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GatsbyJS]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is a new blogging platform GatsbyJS. Currently a work in progress. If you want to create your own blog using GatsbyJS, below are a few…]]></description><link>https://twitter.com/andrewartajos/gatsbyjs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://twitter.com/andrewartajos/gatsbyjs/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 22:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is a new blogging platform GatsbyJS. Currently a work in progress. If you want to create your own blog using GatsbyJS, below are a few resources that will get you started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Gatsby quick start quide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.org/tutorial/&quot;&gt;Gatsby.js tutorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/gatsbyjs/gatsby-starter-blog&quot;&gt;Gatsby starter blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://overreacted.io&quot;&gt;Overreacted&lt;/a&gt; - Dan Abramov’s blog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am happy with what I have right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previously, I used Jekyll. I never progressed learning ruby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gatsby is a Javascript based static site generator. As a front end developer, I feel right at home writing my blog using Gatsby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It makes a lot of sense.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>